American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology records
American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology records
- Series IV. Meetings, 1906-2002; bulk 1934-2002; 29 boxes (42.35 linear feet)
  - Subseries IV.A. Council/Executive Board Meetings, 1906-2002; bulk 1942-2002; 98 folders
    - Minutes, Council and Business Meetings, 1931-1935 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, Council and Business Meetings, 1936-1938 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Minutes, Council and Business Meetings, 1939-1940 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Minutes, Council and Business Meetings, 1941-1942 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Minutes, Council and Business Meetings, 1943 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Minutes, Council and Business Meetings, 1944-1945 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1946 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Minutes, Business Meetings, 1946 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Meeting Minutes/Agendas, 1947-1950 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Minutes, Business Meetings, 1948 & 1949 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1952 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Meeting Minutes/Agendas, 1953/54 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Minutes, Business Meeting, 1953-54 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1955 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Minutes, 1955-56 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1956/57 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1958/59 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Minutes, 1958-59 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Minutes, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - Minutes, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1962 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Minutes, 1962 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 34)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 35)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 36)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 37)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 38)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 39)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 40)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 41)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Minutes & Agenda, Spring 1974 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Minutes & Agenda, Summer/Fall 1974 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Minutes & Agenda, Fall 1975 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Minutes & Agenda, Extraordinary Meeting, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Extraordinary Meeting, Miscellaneous Materials, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1978 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Minutes & Agenda, Spring 1979 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Minutes & Agenda, Fall 1979 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Minutes, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Minutes, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Minutes, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Minutes, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1985 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Minutes, 1985 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1986 (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - Minutes, 1986 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1987 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Minutes & Agenda, 1991 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, December 1942 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1944-46 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1953-54 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1955-56 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1957-58 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1963-65 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1966-68 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1969-71 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1980-81 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Subseries IV.B. Annual Meetings, 1934-1991; bulk 1970-1991; 613 folders
    Boxes 69-84 are arranged chronologically. Boxes 85-88 are arranged according to activity/subject meeting held at annual meeting and then by date.
    - 1934-1941-Proceedings, American Society of Biological Chemists, 1934-1941 (Bound Volume) (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - 1957- 1960 General Correspondence (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - 1962-1973-Dates and Sites of Future FASEB Annual Meetings (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - 1963-Abstract Correspondence, December 1962- March 1963 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - 1963-Lectureships (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - 1964-Abstract Correspondence, December 1963-January 1964 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - 1964-Abstracts, Transferred (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - 1964 Symposium Correspondence (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - 1965-Abstract Correspondence (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - 1965-General Correspondence (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - 1965-Mailings to Members (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - 1966-Abstract Correspondence (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - 1966-Ad hoc Committee, "Experiment" on Programming, 1965-66 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - 1966-General Correspondence (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - 1966-Mailings to Members (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - 1967-Abstract Correspondence (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - 1967-General Correspondence (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - 1967-Insurance Proposal (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - 1967-Mailings to Members (Box 69, Folder 24)
    - 1968-Abstract Correspondence (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - 1968-Abstracts, Transferred (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - 1968-Closed Circuit TV (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - 1968-General Correspondence (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - 1968-Mailings to Members (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - 1969-Abstract Correspondence (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - 1969-Abstract Correspondence (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - 1969-Abstract Correspondence (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - 1969 Abstract Evaluations (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - 1969-General Correspondence (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - 1969-Mailings to Members (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - 1970-Abstract Correspondence (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - 1970-Abstract Correspondence (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - 1970 Abstract Evaluations, Panel 1-30 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - 1970 Abstract Evaluations, Panel 31-60 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - 1970 Abstract Mailings to Members (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - 1970 Abstract Mailings to Members (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - 1970 Abstract Mailings to Members (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - 1970 Abstract Mailings to Members (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - 1970 Abstract Mailings to Members (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - 1970-Abstracts, Transferred (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - 1970-Abstracts, Transferred (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - 1970-General Correspondence (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - 1970-General Correspondence (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - 1970-Mailings to Members (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - 1970 Reception Correspondence (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - 1970-Reception for Robert Marston & William McElroy, Invitations (Box 70, Folder 25)
    - 1970-Symposium, "Mass Spectrometry Course" by James A. McCloskey (Box 70, Folder 26)
    - 1970-Symposium, Materials Distributed for Short Course (Box 70, Folder 27)
    - 1971-Abstract Correspondence (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - 1971-Abstract Correspondence (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - 1971-Abstract Daily Record Sheet (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - 1971-Abstract Forms (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - 1971-Abstracts (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - 1971-Exhibit Information (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - 1971-Exhibits, Steven K. Meeting Management, 1968-69 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Exhibits, Steven K. Herlitz, Inc, Exhibit & Meeting Management, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Exhibits, Steven K. Herlitz, Inc, Exhibit & Meeting Management, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Federation Proceedings & Abstracts (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - 1971-General Correspondence, no date (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - 1971-General Correspondence, May-Dec, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - 1971-General Correspondence, Jan-July, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - 1971-General Correspondence, Aug-Dec, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - 1971-General Correspondence, Jan-March, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - 1971-General Correspondence, April-Dec, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - 1971-Mailings to Members (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - 1971-Planning (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - 1971-Procedures Committee (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - 1971-Site Information, San Francisco (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - 1971-Symposium, Correspondence (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - 1971-Symp., Chairman, Haber (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - 1971-Symp., Chairman, Hirs (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - 1971-Symp., Chairman, Racker (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - 1971-Symp., Chairman, Richardson (Box 71, Folder 25)
    - 1971-Symp., Chairman, Roseman (Box 71, Folder 26)
    - 1971-Symp., Chairman, Van Korff (Box 71, Folder 27)
    - 1971-Symp., Planning (Box 71, Folder 28)
    - 1971-Travel, American Airlines (Box 71, Folder 29)
    - 1971-Travel, Arrangements & Correspondence (Box 71, Folder 30)
    - 1971-Travel, Disneyland Hotel (Box 71, Folder 31)
    - 1972-Abstract Correspondence, Nov-Dec 13, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 32)
    - 1972-Abstract Correspondence, Dec 14-30, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - 1972-Abstract Correspondence, January 1972 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - 1972-Abstract Evaluations (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - 1972-Abstracts (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - 1972-Abstracts, Published, but not presented, part 1 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - 1972-Abstracts, Published, but not presented, part 2 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - 1972-Abstracts, Published (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - 1972-Abstracts, Session Chairmen 1 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - 1972-Abstracts, Session Chairmen 2 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - 1972-Abstracts, Session Chairmen 3 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - 1972-Abstracts, Session Chairmen 4 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - 1972-Abstracts, Session Chairmen 5 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - 1972-Abstracts, Session Chairmen 6 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - 1972-Abstracts, Transferred (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - 1972-Abstracts, Withdrawn (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - 1972-FASEB Information (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - 1972-General Correspondence & Miscellaneous Materials, August 1971-June 1972 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - 1972-Symposium (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - 1972-Symp. Correspondence (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - 1973-Abstract Correspondence, Nov-Dec 15, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - 1973-Abstract Correspondence, Dec 18-29, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - 1973-Abstract Correspondence, Jan-April, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - 1973-Abstracts, Session Chairmen 1 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - 1973-Abstracts, Session Chairmen 2 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - 1973-Abstracts, Session Chairmen 3 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - 1973-Abstracts, Session Chairmen 4 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - 1973-Abstracts, Session Chairmen 5 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - 1973-Abstracts, Session Chairmen 6 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - 1973-Abstracts, Session Chairmen 7 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - 1973-Abstracts, Session Chairmen 8 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - 1973-Abstracts, Session Chairmen 9 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - 1973-Abstracts, Session Chairmen 10 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - 1973-Abstracts, Session Chairmen 11 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - 1973-Abstracts, Transferred (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - 1973-Abstracts, Withdrawn (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - 1973-General Correspondence (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - 1973-Mailings to Members (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - 1973-Special Symposia (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - 1973-Special Symposia, Edsall "Protein Chemistry" (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - 1973-Special Symposia Invitations (5 copies) (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - 973-Symposium (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - 1973-Symposium, ASBC Nobel Laureates, magnetic tape (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - 1974-Abstracts, Correspondence, January 1974 (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - 1974-Abstracts, Correspondence, February 1-12, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - 1974-Abstracts, Correspondence, February 13-20, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - 1974-Abstracts, Correspondence, March 1974 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - 1974-Abstracts, Correspondence, April-June 1974 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 1974-Abstracts, Poster Sessions, B-Cy (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 1974-Abstracts, Poster Sessions, Cy-Ev (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 1974-Abstracts, Poster Sessions, F-Ph (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 1974-Abstracts, Poster Sessions, Ph-T (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - 1974-Abstracts, Session Chairmen, March 1-4, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - 1974-Abstracts, Session Chairmen, March 4-5, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - 1974-Abstracts, Session Chairmen, March 5-6, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - 1974-Abstracts, Session Chairmen, March 6-7, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - 1974-Abstracts, Session Chairmen, March 7, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - 1974-Abstracts, Session Chairmen, March 7-8, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - 1974-Abstracts, Session Chairmen, March 8-11, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - 1974-Abstracts, Session Chairmen, March 11, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - 1974-Abstracts, Session Chairmen, March 11-14, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - 1974-Abstracts, Session Chairmen, March 14-15, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - 1974-Abstracts, Session Chairmen, March 18-20, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - 1974-Abstracts, Session Chairmen, March 21-April 1974 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - 1974-Abstracts, Session Chairmen, April 2-May 9, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - 1974-Exhibits, Agreement, 1971, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - 1974-Exhibits, Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - 1974-Exhibits, Steven K. Herlitz Correspondence, 1970-71 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - 1974-Floor plans, hotels, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - 1974-General Correspondence, no date-May 1972 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - 1974-General Correspondence, July 1972- September 1973 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - 1974-General Correspondence, Oct-Dec 1973 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - 1974-General Correspondence, Jan-March 1974 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - 1974-General Correspondence, April-June 24, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - 1974-General Correspondence, June 25, 1974-May 1975 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - 1974-Poster Session Reports (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - 1974-Poster Session Reports (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - 1974-Program Committee, 1971-73 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - 1974-Site Information, Dallas as an Alternate site, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - 1974-Site Information, Denver, cancelled meeting site, brochures, 1970-71 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - 1974-Site Information, Denver, cancelled meeting site, correspondence, 1969-71 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - 1974-Site Information,1973 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - 1974-Symp., Miscellaneous Materials, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - 1974-Symp., Ts'o's Public Policy Symposium, 1973-75 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - 1975-Abstract Correspondence, Nov-Dec 1974 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - 1975-Abstract Correspondence, Dec 1974-Jan 1975 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - 1975-Abstract Correspondence, Jan-July 1975 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - 1975-Abstracts, Transferred from ASBC (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - 1975-Abstracts, Transferred to ASBC (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - 1975-General Correspondence, 1974-75 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - 1975-Mini-symposium (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - 1975-Office of Scientific Meetings, Helena B. Lemp Files, 1974-1975 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - 1975-Poster Sessions, 1973-76 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - 1975-Poster Session Survey (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - 1975-Poster Session Survey (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - 1975-Symposium, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - 1976-Abstract Correspondence, Not Accepted, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - 1976-Abstract Correspondence, Recieved too later, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - 1976-Abstract Correspondence, Withdrawn, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - 1976-Budget/Expenses (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - 1976-Courtesy Associates, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - 1976-General Correspondence, 1972-74 (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - 1976-General Correspondence, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - 1976-General Correspondence, Jan-Feb 9, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - 1976-General Correspondence, Feb 10-19, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - 1976-General Correspondence, Feb 20-March 1976 (Box 76, Folder 23)
    - 1976-General Correspondence, April-May 1976 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - 1976-General Correspondence, June 1976 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - 1976-Floor Plans, 1975-76 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - 1976-Lectures, Opening (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - 1976-Menus (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - 1976-Program Committee, 1975-76 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - 1976-Special Functions, Mini-symposia, no date- March 8, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - 1976-Special Functions, Mini-symposia, March-July 1976 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - 1976-Special Functions, Public Policy Symp., 1976 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - 1976-Travel/Transportation, 1971-73, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - 1977-Abstract Correspondence, Oct 1976-April 1977 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - 1977-Abstracts, Transferred (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - 1977-Abstracts, Withdrawn (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - 1977-Foreign Plenary Lecturers, February 1977 (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - 1977-General Correspondence, Nov 1975-Feb 1977 (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - 1977-General Correspondence, March-July 1977 (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - 1977- Lectures, Opening (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - 1977-Special Functions, Mini-symposia, Chairmen and Schedule (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - 1978-Abstract Correspondence, Jan 3-June 1, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 19)
    - 1978-Budget, Financial Statements, Etc (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - 1978-Contracts, License Agreement/Insurance (Box 77, Folder 21)
    - 1978-Exhibits, Steven K. Herlitz, Checks (Box 77, Folder 22)
    - 1978-Exhibits, Steven K. Herlitz, Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 77, Folder 23)
    - 1978-Exhibits, Steven K. Herlitz, Expenses (Box 77, Folder 24)
    - 1978-Exhibits, Steven K. Herlitz, Installment Commission Statement (Box 77, Folder 25)
    - 1978-General Correspondence, Oct 1975-Dec 1977 (Box 77, Folder 26)
    - 1978-General Correspondence, Jan-June 1978, April 1979 (Box 77, Folder 27)
    - 1978-Lecturers (Box 77, Folder 28)
    - 1978-LKB Brochure Correspondence (Box 77, Folder 29)
    - 1978-Mailings to Members (Box 77, Folder 30)
    - 1978-Poster and Slide Session Statistics (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - 1978-Poster Committee (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - 1978-Reception Invitations/Correspondence (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - 1978-Site Information, Washington, D.C., Cancelled Site (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - 1978-Special Function Forms (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - 1978-Special Functions, Mini-symposium, Chairmen Guidelines (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - 1978-Special Functions, Mini-symposium, Programs (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - 1979-Abstract Correspondence, Dec1978-May 1979 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - 1979-Abstract Processing Instructions and Program Summary (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - 1979-Abstracts, late/withdrawn (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - 1979-Abstracts, Revised/Replaced/Transferred (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - 1979-Abstracts, Withdrawn (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - 1979-General Correspondence, Dec1977-Dec 1978 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - 1979-General Correspondence (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - 1979-Housing (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - 1979-Lectures, Opening (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - 1979-Meeting Notices (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - 1979-Office of Scientific Meetings, Correspondence,1978-1979 (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - 1979-Paper Presentation Rules and Topics (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - 1979-Program Committee (Box 78, Folder 20)
    - 1979-Reception, President's (Box 78, Folder 21)
    - 1979-Slide Session, Chairmen Instructions (Box 78, Folder 22)
    - 1979-Special Functions, Mini-symposia, Invited Speakers (Box 78, Folder 23)
    - 1979-Special Functions, Mini-symposia, Chairmen (Box 78, Folder 24)
    - 1979-Special Functions, Symp., Chairmen Speakers (Box 78, Folder 25)
    - 1979-Special Function Forms (Box 78, Folder 26)
    - 1980-Abstract Rules/Processing (Box 78, Folder 27)
    - 1980-Abstracts, Returned/Withdrawn (Box 78, Folder 28)
    - 1980-Abstracts, Revised, Replacements, etc (Box 78, Folder 29)
    - 1980-Budget/Expenses, 1974-June 1980 (Box 78, Folder 30)
    - 1980-Budget/Expenses, July 1980-Feb 1981 (Box 78, Folder 31)
    - 1980-Budget/Expenses, Bank Accounts, Invoice Correspondence (Box 78, Folder 32)
    - 1980-Call for Papers, drafts, proofs, etc (Box 78, Folder 33)
    - 1980-Contracts (Box 78, Folder 34)
    - 1980-Convention Information (Box 78, Folder 35)
    - 1980-Correspondence, Biophysical Society, March 1976-Dec 1979 (Box 78, Folder 36)
    - 1980-Correspondence, Biophysical Society, Dec 1976-Sept 1980 (Box 78, Folder 37)
    - 1980-Correspondence, Biophysical Society, John Wolff, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - 1980-Correspondence, Joint-Meeting, 1974-79 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - 1980-Exhibits, Correspondence, Jan 1979-May 1980 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - 1980-Exhibit Information (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - 1980-FASEB Placement Service (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - 1980-Floor Plan 1 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - 1980-Floor Plan 2 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - 1980-General Correspondence, 1972-79 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - 1980-General Correspondence, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - 1980-Housing Correspondence, 1978-79 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - 1980-Housing Correspondence, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - 1980-Insurance, Coverage (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - 1980-Mailings to Members (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - 1980-Meeting Management (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - 1980-Office of Scientific Meetings, Correspondence, 1979-80 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - 1980-Plenary Lecturers (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - 1980-Program Committee (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - 1980-Program Committee, Complaints & Suggestions (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - 1980-Program Planning (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - 1980-Reception, President's (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - 1980-Registration (Complimentary) (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - 1980-Site Information, Rivergate Hilton-Marriott (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - 1980-Site Information, The Rivergate Exhibition Center (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - 1980-Special Functions (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - 1980-Special Functions, Hold for Room Assignments (Box 79, Folder 25)
    - 1980-Special Functions, Mini-symposium, Chairmen, Selected Abstracts (Box 79, Folder 26)
    - 1980-Special Functions, Mini-symposium, Correspondence and Schedules (Box 79, Folder 27)
    - 1980-Special Functions, Mini-symposium, Invited Speakers Program (Box 79, Folder 28)
    - 1980-Special Functions, Symp., Correspondence (Box 79, Folder 29)
    - 1980-Special Functions, Symp., Invited Speakers (Box 79, Folder 30)
    - 1980-Special Functions, Symp., June 1-4, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 31)
    - 1980-Travel, Arrangements (Box 79, Folder 32)
    - 1981-Abstract Correspondence (Box 79, Folder 33)
    - 1981-Abstract Proceedings (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - 1981-Abstracts, Memo to File (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - 1981-Abstracts, Replacements/Corrections (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 1981-Abstracts, Withdrawn (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 1981-Contracts, Agreements/Leases/Proposals (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 1981-Budget and Expenses/Meeting Invoices (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - 1981-Exhibits, Correspondence (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - 1981-Exhibits, Exhibitors Checks (Box 80, Folder 8)